since manulife launched income plus its
success has been extraordinary this is
because income plus offers retirees and
those nearing retirement exactly what
they are looking for predictable and
sustainable income as well as the
opportunity for growth with its income
guarantee income plus can help provide
predictable retirement income that is
protected from market downturns
sustainable income that will last for
your life or for the lives of you and
your spouse and potentially increasing
guaranteed income to help keep pace with
inflation income plus also allows you to
benefit from guaranteed lifetime income
as early as age 55 because investment
growth is also important income plus
offers a broad choice of over 40
investment funds from many of canada's
top fund managers you have the
flexibility to move between funds and
fund managers should your needs or
preferences change and you always have
access to your money in case you need it
whether you're just beginning to think
about or are already enjoying retirement
there's a lot to consider watch the
videos here on retirement risks to learn
more about the challenges you may face
the case study videos will then show you
how income plus can help meet your
retirement income needs you can find out
more about the benefits of income plus
by speaking with your advisor or by
clicking on the income plus client
brochure